

## **Xavier Hernandez-Martinez**

# Web Developer

(+33) 6 26 09 19 66 xhernan.martinez@gmail.com www.xhernandez.me linkedin.com/in/xavihrez github.com/XavHernandez

### **Profile**

Web Developer, product oriented, with 10 years of experience as LiveOps manager for the french iGaming market leader. Eager to work, contribute, learn, and develop skills with both Ruby on Rails and Javascript. Good soft skills, fluent English, open to relocation.

### **Skills**

{
Ruby,
Ruby on Rails,
JavaScript ES6,
HTML5 / CSS3,
Bootstrap,
SQLite,
PostgreSQL,
Git,
Github,
Heroku,
}

## Experience

#### ONLINE OPERATIONS MANAGER

WINAMAX | PARIS, FR | JUL 2010 - SEPT 2019

- Orchestrated launch for products and promotions with development and creative teams.
- Managed product backlog to optimize game client and products.
- Collaborated with development teams to optimize back-office tools.
- Designed, deployed and managed full online gaming offers (schedule and money flow).

#### **ONLINE MARKETING EXECUTIVE**

WINAMAX | LONDON, UK | AUG 2009 - JUN 2010

- Coordinated with B2B providers and customer support to manage gaming events.
- Created and maintained online content materials for products, promotions and game client.
- Deployed and managed gaming offers for french online communities.

### **Education**

Le Wagon Bordeaux - Full Stack Web Development CODING BOOTCAMP Q2 - 2021

Kagilum / Wensei - Professional SCRUM Certification September 2020

Universite Bordeaux III - Information & Communication DUT Information & Communication Sustainable Development Option 2007 - 2008